It has begun.
Yes, good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
We are here at the morning chime, we are the new art school.
Yes.
Hinenaka is going to make an emergency video presentation,
There's also a past announcement.
It's been planned for quite a while.
What is an emergency?
Urgent is urgent.
So, today is with Ayaka,
It's a little bit different from tonight's urgent theme,
It's not in the world.
Thanks, since a while ago.
Those two are rehearsing for the play.
The three of them.
The one tonight.
It was an emergency.
Tonight's number 3 is vertical,
How's that?
It's on the eye screen,
No, it's vertical.
What is it?
It's not right,
It's okay.
Let them look at it horizontally.
But now..,
Huh?
Huh?Huh?
Now, if you put the two of them vertically...
It's like Emma Yuna's stage, or rather, Emma's presence is so strong.
Oh! I see!
That's what the rumors are saying.
That's fine.
Did you write it with your voice?
Hi Rice! Is that what he's saying?
High rice!
Sac rice!
I have no idea what it sounds like.
The role names are good, aren't they?
The role names are a bit, well, unusual.
The name of the Shinsengumi.
Where is that in there, too?
Yes, it's in there.
Well, Isami Ashito and Hijikata Koshiedo.
Isamiashiashi to hijikata koshiedo. Yes.
It's standing up.
You come home very tired.
My muscles are sore.
Because, you know, I'm walking so much Uchimoto.
Because, you know, I'm walking really neigboringly.
What makes you walk inwardly?
What if we walk on the inside?
Both of you have sore muscles?
Yuna?
Yuna's not... She's already walking on the inside.
That's not how it works. It's such an inner source.
It's so meh, it's so Uchimoto.
I didn't know it rotated like this.
But the practice was getting more and more intense,
For example, when Yuna said "Yuna" with her finger, Emma didn't know what to say,
Emma didn't know what to say, but she said, "You have to smile, come in. It's like she's being made to smile.
I'm looking forward to it. I think there are still tickets for the morning show.
I was still standing there. I don't know why.
I'll just keep doing this.
What do you think of the audience? How does this look?
This is fine. Let's see. Is it sideways now?
It's flowing in the comments. If it's this way, yes.
It's vertical now. Mom says it's landscape.
Are you okay? I came here to tell you this is fine.
Why don't you just make it vertical? How about this?
With this, you can just pull it out.
I can at least hit it with this.
Vertical is fine. There are 2,500 people here.
He said, "Vertical is fine. Have you ever been taken for a ride?
It's better to have them stand up. We're running the video on an emergency basis.
That's right. Because there is an urgency here.
It looks like we can afford it. That's it already.
Decide already. Let's move it. I'll decide.
Stop going around in circles. I heard it's going to stop.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Side again. That's right.
Wait a minute.
I don't know. There's still a bit of a lag.
I'm doing it myself.
Here you go. October is already back today,Here you go. October has already returned today,
Another year is almost over.
Christmas tree.
Looks like fun.
Do you have any big news for us?
Big news?
I'm back.
Where did you go?
Thailand.
Why did you say you were in Thailand while you were there?
I'm very close.
Yes, it is.
I went to Phuket.
Phuket, the most powerful Phuket.
The moment Cocona sent me the pictures, I said, "This is Phuket, right?
She told me that Mie-chan followed me too.
She also sent me pictures of her meals.
The Kaman Gai was so delicious.
It was delicious.
I love Thai food so much.
Phuket is far away. It's far away. It's far away.
Phuket is here, right?
I haven't been to Phuket.
We didn't go to Phuket.
We went there. Patta, right? We went to Pattaya.
Phuket and the floating market.
Patta, right?
Yes. If Mr. Kobayashi didn't drink Phuket and Floating Market, I thought he just drank at Influenggi. I thought they were in the same lineage.
Phuket is the name of the place.
Phuket is a local market.Phuket is a regional market.
Water market location but activity.
Then it's a quiz.
Yes. Last quiz.
The last one.
Um, yes.
What is it?
You know what?
It's good.
No, it's not. Um-i. No, it's not. Do you have a "Hello" in Pokemon?
Oh, so it's "Sawadie Car. Sawadie car? Uh-oh. Then eat this.
What? Why after the commercial? I mean, you know... It's delicious! Tasty.
I didn't get the whole "Ajinomoto" thing. Ajinomoto? They didn't tell you? No, they didn't.
When I go to Phuket. Oh, you mean the Japanese you know. Ah.
Oh, you mean the Japanese you know. Okay, rice seasoning. In a cup made by Ajinomoto. Oh, wow.
Oh, yeah. What was that? Tom Yum Moo.
Ajinomoto and all those things were mainstream.
When I walked around with the image of Japanese people as "ajinomoto," people would call me "ajinomoto, ajinomoto.
Is that what they say? My friend wrote "PrimaHam.
The masses don't know it either.
Let me change the subject a bit and talk about this past year in Ebichu.
This year? I know we're supposed to make the 10 biggest news stories of the year, but there may not even be 10.
What? Stock 9?
The most impressive one was the Evionice one.
That was last year. In junior high.
What? Ohilokone's December stage, December.
This year, it's different.
It's different.
Then, this time,
Great reference.Great reference.
You don't mean that everyone else has been there?
Yes, they did.
In February.
Katsumaru.
Shrimp tour? Shrimp tour, yes.
It's been a long time since I've been on a shrimp tour, and it's been five years since I've been on a shrimp tour.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
How's it going?
I'm still involved in the tour, so when Cocona sang "Punchy Punchy," I thought it was Okinawa,
I thought it was in Okinawa.
Where?
There it is.
From the room we were staying in when we went to the photo book,
I went from the room where we were staying to the room where the costumes were prepared, and changed,
When we left, we went back to the room where the costumes were prepared,
Then they would change into their own clothes and return to their own rooms.
But then, poof, I guess I wanted to be dressed up.
The moment I changed into my clothes, I realized that I had not worn my own shoes,
Oh, you wore a sleeper?
Yes. But I didn't think it was fashionable.
They didn't go with my current outfit.
So I told her I had some cute boots.
Your boots?
Oh, that's right.
They were Mirren's boots.
I didn't buy my boots.
Is that okay?
Okay.
What were they? That. What was that? That.
I forgot I wore it in a sleeper and it looked so much like my boots.
They don't look alike! Not at all.
Not at all. The heels plus the brightness is different.
But, surely, you liked the direction of taste.
Yes, I do.
I'm going to do a temporary pack.
But I didn't have my boots, so I was going to wear coconuts,
But then I realized, "Oh no,
I said yes,
But at that moment, I realized that coconuts are funny.
I mean, there's still a part of me that's hiding, you know?
I see.
I mean, it's there and it's there, but it was a shock.
But this year, it's gradually faded away, coconut.
I see.
Yes, yes.
I thought you didn't know.
I don't think they know.
I'm wearing so much white,
Hey, hey, hey, you know, I had on boots,
All of that?
I was really sleepwalking.
They really did know they were my boots.
Yes, that was one of those times.
Was it tough on the site in Okinawa after that?
Yes, it was. Morning, morning, morning.
I didn't answer the phone early.
I went to bed early.
I went to bed early.I went to bed early.
So.
So now,
I don't even know.
I mean, how many days have I slept?
I'm pretty tired, I'm sure.
So, it's, like, really, really, really emotional,
I think it's kind of funny coconut.
But the face, the face is the most, the face wants to be shocked the most, more than I do.
You know, the things that get hard.
I was like, well, let's regenerate it, but the face, wait,
It's super delicious, it's gone.
And you did it right, didn't you?
I was having a great time with the supermarket and all.
I was so surprised.
I was so amused.
I've been to Okinawa twice.
Yes, you have been twice.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, you didn't get in, did you?
That's right.
I ate water. Kamachan.
Thank you.
I'll be able to go to various places on the spring tour, so I'm not sure if Corona is the right place for me.
Is the ban on vocal performances going to be lifted this year? Maybe from this year.
And at regular gigs too.
Did you do it on the first day of the first tour? The first day.
Matsuoka.
Matsuoka. That's when it really hit me.
Was it the part where I got goosebumps?Was it the part where I get goose bumps?
What?
I don't even remember the venue, but I got a big kick out of it.
Wait a minute.
You know, hall tours, hall tours, basically all of them, are not "otari" type. It's shocking.
Yes, it's true.
What did you think? I heard that you can speak out, speak out.
No, with that.
Oh, you're blue.
Oh, blue.
How was Makuhari? Was I not allowed to speak out at that time?
It was no good. It was no good. Not yet.
No good.
Osaka.
Yes, that one.
Hiroshima?
That one.
That's Kamikorei.
That's Castle. First time at Castle.
Oh, yes... Oh, yes, it's Osaka.
It was a one-man show, wasn't it?
Yes, yes.
It was great.
Like "Love Summa" and "Charisma" by Kool Ali. I wonder if it was a song like this.
I've seen them in videos, but I've never heard them in person.I've seen them in the Cole Silonarmon videos, but I'd never actually heard them before.
You kinda forgot about our last one. I remembered the singer's part,
I remembered so much.
Some of the audience may have forgotten or don't know about it.
This is going to sound very personal, but there was a lot of jail in the 14 stories in January,
There was also a prison in the spring tea ceremony,
I thought, "Well, I was in jail for about six months,
Who stays in jail for six months or so?
Usually they were in there, so the jail connection was a personal goof.
You have to feel emo in that.
That's why he said jail.
That was interesting.
It was fun.
I was shaking.
You can't say "Shikoku"?
Yes, I can't say Shikoku.
It was too funny.
Yes, it was.
Gonyaga mask.
Is there anything else? It was impressive.
Not the spring tour, but a look back at the year, like December.
Overseas? New Zealand.
You didn't have any last words while you were there?
It's been a long time since I've voiced the Familien. I don't know the order of the impressive ones.
When I was in Fameen, I was in a hotel, in the middle of the forest or something, and clouds would appear.
There would be three or four real clouds in the room.
Then, the one that is the strongest for the fetus is Yu.
Yu had grown up in nature.
So you're not afraid of insects at all? I'm totally fine. In the outside world.
I was doing it on the side.We were doing it on the side.
We didn't allow it.
We had to forgive them.
We were saying, "Okay," and throwing towels and stuff.
It was so loud.
It fell into my nose together.
I got up and we were doing this,
And then it just popped off, and I was thinking how many times I wanted to tickle it,
And then the spider started to whirr.
And it was like a whirring sound.
And it was a whirring sound.
Yu was the biggest one.
I really squawked at Yutaka.
Can you get cockroaches with a kokubo?
No cockroaches. I vacuum them up.
I'll vacuum them up.
They're strong.
That's why you can't get close to them.
It's usually impossible.
If you vacuum it up, what's it doing in the vacuum cleaner?
Keep sucking in the Magnum or something.
That's strong.
I've never vacuumed.
You wrap it in a tissue and flush it down the toilet.
What?
What? No?
I can't get it. I can't grab it. I can't get it.
But what are we gonna do? What are we gonna do? Like this.
Spray.
What do I do?What should I do?
What do I do?
If you spray them at that moment, they'll lay eggs right then.
What?
They lay eggs and then die.
That's right. They die after they lay eggs.
Oh, no.
But, because, you know, it's just like a gokijit.
You have to fight them with that.
It's best to use a face-killing spray.
What? What's that?
There's a spray that kills cockroaches,
It can even kill cockroaches.
Wow.
Ha-ha-ha.
Seriously? For real?
I found it. I've got to try it.
I see.
And he said, "I want to see Tokozilla. I went to Korea to see Tokozilla,
I was in Korea, and Mr. Fujii sent me a video saying, "Be careful watching Tokozilla,
He sent me a TikTok-like video.
He sent me a TikTok video. When I first heard that I was going, I was curious.
Are you really going? Tokojira-jira-jira.
There it is. Because that's the thing. If I went out to the house,
If you go out to the house, it's like burning all the clothes in the house. That's the level.
It seems that they are in really dirty places,
Even in sauna facilities,
But there are places that have been around for a long time that have been ruined because of it.
I don't know what you mean by that.
They're called "tokozirabi," but they're turtles.It's called a tokozirabi, but it's a kamebushi.
Turtles are big, aren't they?
A stink bug is about the same size as a stink bug, and it stings and sucks blood.
They suck blood when they sting you.
And the bitten part itches.
It's something that's come to Japan now, too.
Osaka
Oh, no!
They got in when I was packing my white clothes and stuff.
It got in there, didn't it? Oh, man.
But I've never been out in the light.
It was like 2:00 or 3:00 in the morning.
I'd come out in the dark, bobbing and weaving.
No, I mean, if you sleep with the light on...
I was just saying, you know, if you sleep with the light on.
That sounds like me.
Do you think the costume looks good?
I can see it.
I mean, is it even that big?
Where's the glare?
I can't go anywhere.
Six or five a day, even for Tamaki.
That's crazy.
But when I told my friends...
I don't know where it is.
I'm in a dirty place, but I think I'll be okay.
I'm sure it's fine.
It's like once.
I don't need the flooring.
Oh.Aww.
That was a great bug story.
Can I ignore that?
What?
Okay, let's just ignore it. One time.
Can I ignore it here?
What?
What happened next?
She wants me to tell you my story and then we can go back to it.
It's not going over very well, to be honest.
My idol's talking about bugs.
Tell them about New Zealand.
New Zealand's another country.
It's not that different.
The hardest part was that it was cold.
But that was only on the day of the show, wasn't it?
The day of the concert
Cold
It's out! It's out!
What happened?
What's wrong with Areka?
She's throwing away all our stuff.
How do I say this?
I don't know...
My carry-on's getting full.
Get rid of all your stuff.
All your clothes... Like the clothes you're wearing.
Back to Japan.
I can't believe I'm going back to Japan.
Why did you do that?
Ayaka's the best at packing.
You're a minimalist.
But I want to get rid of the stuff I don't need at home, too.
She said...
You know, like underwear.
You have a lot of used stuff.
We all have them.
Here, before you take a bath, you say, "I'm off.
Take it off.
Like that.
I don't need it.
I threw it away when I came back.
I'm sorry.
As a result...
I came home.
You bought me something I didn't need.
What the hell is that?
I have to go back.
What's that?
A hand-me-down shirt.
I've heard that story before.
We've all seen that one.
They're all looking.
I thought you were straight ahead.
You're so excited.
If I had it, I'd throw it away so much.If you have it, you can throw it away so much.
That's as far as I wanted to go.
I just wanted to get home with that much less stuff.
I wanted to go home with a bag full of bread.
I'm... I'm... I'm...
That's right.
I was comped before I even got there.
They had me at 20 kilograms.
I mean...
I mean, 19.7 kilograms...
That's crazy.
I only have 300 grams left.
25 kilograms.
23kg
I only have 300 grams left!
I only have 300g left!
At the station
I only have 300g at the station
Because New Zealand wine is famous!
Because New Zealand wine is famous.
You bought it, didn't you?
It was delicious.
I thought for sure you'd go to the tranch and you wouldn't make it.
That's right, because it was on my side.
But I thought I couldn't weigh 15.9 kg on the way back.
But I thought we couldn't weigh 15.9kg.
I'm splitting it with you guys.
I'm splitting it at my place.I'm splitting it at my place.
I'm splitting it at my place
We're splitting it at everyone's place.
It's not just the house stuff.
I've lightened my load.
I'm getting lighter.
I don't have a house.
I have no home.
I don't have a home, I don't have a home, I don't have a home...
Thanks to all of you
Thanks to all of you.
Was Carrie okay?
What did you take?
I brought all my stuff, in case you were wondering.
Why? Why?
Why?
I'm on edge.
Not that much.
It's not like you needed to bring that much personal stuff.
You didn't need that thing that the P.O.W. brought.
It was there.
There it is.
It's here.
It's there.
Which way?
I've been looking everywhere.
The mountain is with the humans.
Just a little bit.Just a second.
There it is.
Oh, shit.
Please take it.
Let's see what you got.
NA file.
100-millimeter file.
Maybe something like this.
Let's hope.
Patras are not so easy to find.
A little, well, scary guy with a cell phone that looks like this.
Translation app?
He says he loves your fashion sense.
It's true.
I'm helping you.
I'm confused.
You were supposed to be a sniper.
You were very popular.
Tele-traveler.
I'm a sniper. That's fine. I'm taking over.
You look like a hero.
And the family, too. Purple.
I used to study colors.
I was studying.
I think so.
No, but it's a hard place to get to.
I was just thinking Japanese.I'm sorry, is that Japanese?
Playing in such a windy place!
I probably would have canceled the show if it was in Japan.
There's been so many warnings all week.
It's not my event.
I wouldn't have made that decision.
But I did it because the organizer got hit.
The wind was blowing like that.
I think the winds were so strong in Japan that the school opened up.
I couldn't break the window, so it was like a fast-paced event.
Somebody said Mike's windshield rolled down, right?
I did.
When Cocona's windshield flew away, I went to get it.
I told him I was sweating because I was overseas.
You're welcome.
That feels good.
That was so embarrassing.
That's pretty embarrassing.
It's pretty embarrassing.
There were a lot of Japanese.
Of course, it's Japan Fest.
There were a lot of Japanese people there.
And of course the fans who came from Japan.
Thank you very much for the 30 or so people who came.
It's very rare for fans to come all the way to New Zealand.
It's something I've never experienced before.
We want to do it in a place where we can be tested.
Maybe we want to do it in a place where we can be tested.
No, the audience...No, I've got a client.
I want to go to South America or something.
I've never been.
I've never been. I've never been.
I'm an Okeladist.
An Okeladist.
How long have I been an Okeladist?
About 7 years.
Seven years is not so easy.
I've been thinking a lot about the pain of the sea, making one from zero.
I remember the beginning in the center.
Everyone in the center was so inquisitive in the beginning.
I think so, but I'm sure that as we go through the process, we will come to understand many things.
I think we'll find that we should have done this, we should have done that.
Are you done?
I'm looking at the comments, and I'm thinking about something else right now.
I'm glad you took it.
Thank you very much.
I wish we could do this every year.
Can we do it again in a thousand years?
You know...
I don't know...
Is there a way to teach new things?
Yes, new things, but more than that, we have to do many things
You can't just stay the same.
That's absolutely wrong.
That's why I've been thinking that I have to change.
I don't have a lot of money. I don't need a lot of money.
I thought maybe you dropped the booby prize... that day...
I know it's weird, but I had a lot of fun this year.I had a great time this year, even though it was a boo-boo.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I had a really good time.
I'll never forget it.
I'm not doing all of them, but I'll give it one more shot.
I'm not doing all of it, but one more hit, and then you say, "Let's take off our clothes.
Hmm...
You tell me I'm getting bigger or more advanced, but I haven't changed at all.
Then you can tell me about Arthur's day at the Bluffer's.
You feel like a kid.
I'll do it with a killer.
I've always loved you as a big boy, but I still don't understand what you're talking about.
I don't know yet, but I'm getting there, and I'm probably more mature now.
I want to talk to him. He hasn't gotten any taller.
I appreciate you telling me to say that.
Love.
I was going to do that with the book, but it's Arthur's fault.
It's Arthur's fault.
I see... you cut it off.
You know, I think I have a lot of stuff to buy.
I'm sure there's a lot to buy, but... it's on sale when we record it.
No?
Sorry.
I'm sorry, I just... I don't know...
I mean, what's the big news?
Isn't it good that it's all the same?
What have I been doing for a year?
A year?A year?
We've been playing a lot of shows.
We've been doing two man shows again, haven't we?
Two man series
I think we had more shows than last year.
It's kind of like the Corona has been lifted.
I think there were more shows than last year.
I guess there were a lot of summer festivals.
For the first time in a long time, we were on Mezamashi Live,
And we got sandwiched in.
Lucky and a little lucky.
For now,
I'm scared.
Well, it would be really interesting if we start now,
I was in a great hurry during the Mezamashi Live.
I was always in a hurry at the Mezamashi Live,
Before the live,
You know...us,
After we did the menso, we did the Nakayama time, and then we assembled the engine,
Nakayama time, and then the engine is assembled.
Yes, once we accept,
And then we would calm down,
I was quite, I don't know...,
I was asked to meditate in another room to calm myself down.
And I'll be in this room when I'm done,
I told him to calm down,I told them to calm down separately,
When I was called on, everyone was already up on their sleeves.
Oh no, I felt it.
Oh no, how, why, why, what did they say to me?
I don't know anymore.
I think I was in a great hurry.
He meditated alone for a long time. He was in the wrong room,
He said he put me down.
He was trying to calm me down. He put me down.
You know, I haven't always meditated.
I want to stop.
The manager was trying to do that,
Maybe people have forgotten about it.
I don't have my fingers on that side, either,
I don't have any fingers. I don't have any fingers,
I guess we were all too busy to help.
We're in too much of a hurry to think.
Dad, maybe you need to go to the bathroom.
But I can't hold it,
That's not what I'm saying.
I can't.
I can't hold it. I'll tell you!
Take it with you.
I was in a huge hurry for the first few songs.
That was my biggest trouble.
Well, not really trouble, more of an accident.
I can hear you, you know.
I was in a hurry.
I said, "You're saying that now? I said, "You're telling me now?
I said, "I'm going to tell you right now.He said, "You say that really fast.
That's it, that's it.
Musha Shugyo free live concert, this year?
This year.
This year?
This year, this year.
This year.
Since February.
It goes by so fast, doesn't it? I see.
You don't even have a performer. I'm retracing my steps.
It feels like a long time ago. It's the same level.
It feels like a long time ago. About two years ago.
It was also the first training live when you finally touched me. You guys have been waiting for us.
Even this year, we're still doing our own shows, like Seven Park.
We did. We haven't done that in a long time.
We're doing the Furila again. I want to do it again. I want to do it again.
But the Kanazawa performance was really good. You know, that was a lot of work.
You know, they set up the stage in the middle of nowhere. It was like a petit famie.
It wasn't a free concert. I'd rather have a stage for a free show.
But we did a few times there. We did it twice. I want to do it, I want to do it.
I did it twice. It's a place that appears in textbooks called "paradise" or something like that.
There was a big expanse of grass in front of the place, and it was really nice.
It's a big place. It was really beautiful.
Sonny didn't say, "Let's do that.
It's like a Gundam Plaza. Gundam Plaza.
When was the last time you did that?
The playlist was cold. I remember it was cold.
It's not a place where you can play Frilla. I would like to do it again.
What about Taiyo-oka? Taiyo-oka, yes. How about Taiyo-oka? Taiyo-oka is, you know.
The Frila place in Kyoto. Yes! Yes! Yes!
We didn't do it. But there are a lot of people who are still in the same two or three people from that time.
It was so much cooler than that day, wasn't it?
It was so much tighter.
It was really tight.
It was about 10 years ago.
Ten years ago.
I guess they were talking about 10 years ago.
And the in-person benefit, starting this year.
Yes, that's right.
You did the face-to-face, right?
Yes, we did.
It was so much fun.
The response time was great.
What did we do? What was that?
What did we do?
Joint.
Well, it's a relationship with commerce.
Trade? Joint.
Yes, we did.
Where did you do it?
With a lot of people, like at the International Exhibition Center.
It was a joint event, wasn't it?
Oh, me too.
Oh, that?
That?
It's a joint exhibition hall.
Did you get the trade? Here.
Yes, I did.I took it.
I took it.
I took it in the samurai training.
I remember the samurai training. I remember that.
Did you do it together?
We did it together.
That was a joint project?
Yes, we did.
What?
We worked together for quite a long month,
We also took the costumes for the tour,
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
Oh, yeah.
How's that?
Big side, shift.
Right.
You did it with Big Side and Pasikko. Pasico is the headquarters of Sony Electric Race. Right.
And, oh, I just remembered. I sent Emma home. I don't know.
Yeah, you did. You too, Emma. She wasn't feeling well, so I dropped her off.
You scared me. Emma. That's the big side. Big side. I don't know.
No, I don't. I mean, Emma, she's been asking me about it all day, and I've been driving her home.
I remember now. Yeah. She didn't have her usual smile.
What, were you at a restaurant? Yeah. We split up. Split. Split.
Split. Split. Split.
It's too different from what you mean by "fork off. Divide and conquer.
Next year is our 15th anniversary year.
That's right.
Our major debut will be our 10th anniversary, and the 10th anniversary of our formation will be the Music Fest.Our major debut was on our 10th anniversary, and the 10th anniversary of our formation was the Music Fest.
Has it been five years? Five years have passed.
I see. That's a great year.
Did you draw?
We all have money.
Two and a half years.
Is it two and a half years yet?
May 5th, 2021. What?
May 2020?
We'll be together for two more years.
21, I guess.
When I think about it, there was a corona.
We had a long period of time where we didn't have dinner together.
Dinner is a great way to make memories, isn't it?
I think we will have a lot of meals this year.
This year, I suddenly felt a surge of energy.
Where was the best meal you had this year?
Like my sister's ice cream in Osaka.
Let's go there.
Yu definitely likes ponzu (Japanese sauce made with soy sauce and citrus juice).
It was really good.
It was good there, too. Fukuoka.
What did you eat?
It's Monday in Tororo's bed.
Oh, I'm not here.
Why am I not here?
Mino-chan wasn't here.
You were away for work or something.
Because Hiroshima was delicious, too. Because Hiroshima was good, too.
Hiroshima was delicious.
I was in Hiroshima.
About two days ago.
We ate this together.
Cutting.
It's like we've been going to the same restaurant for a long time.
That's true.
You were there when I was a staff member.
Speaking of Hiroshima, there's nothing to hold you back.
I've been in touch.
I still want to eat this pizza baked goods the most, I do.
You don't have anything like that?
You eat it, right?
If I could eat anything, I would eat Hiroshima.
I'm going to eat Hiroshima.
What do you like?
Hokkaido's delicious hokke?
Hokke? It was really good.
Where did you go in Hokkaido this year?
Tomakomai.
Tomakomai!
Tomakomai was delicious!
My favorite is Tomakomai!
Tomakomai!
Of all the places I've been on tour.
Tomakomai is the best place I've been on tour.
The town is so small.
But you guys... But Yu no tachi
Iwamoto members arrived the day before.
We said, "What should we do about dinner?
They said we should go somewhere free.
So we looked where to go.
There was an AEON about 30 minutes' walk away.
So we decided to walk there.
It took another 30 minutes and I was tired.
I went to Hachipan shop and so on.
I started going to Hokkaido to go to the Aeon.
And we ended up going to a sushi restaurant that we passed by.
We went there.
It was so good!
It was really good, but...
It's huge!
I love it.
It's like three plates about this high.
It's really, really easy to eat.
Who will eat the most?
Who eats the most?
What do you think?
I think it's Nonaka.
Axle is the best eater.
Nonaka's coming?
He's coming!
If it's just us...
We'll eat all kinds of food.
It's hard to keep up with all the food coming out.
When I look over there, most of the plates are gone. When I look over there, most of the plates are gone.
I'm starting to feel like I'm putting food away.
That's exactly what I was doing when I was hitting the pets.
Mirei was feeling a little under the weather that day.
She couldn't drink.
So our group was pretty much divided into two groups.
And the non-drinkers.
That way.
Mirei wasn't able to eat anything when she was there.
Everyone likes to go fast.
This is better.
I'm the best eater.
I did.
I was the best eater.
Here you go.
But thank you... for a bowl of rice.
It was the same in Akita.
I didn't see a lot of them.
Akita, you had a lot of reservations.
That was simply because the number of people who made reservations was too small.
We were too few for the number of reservations.
In other words, too much food was served.
Aya and I ate 4 portions by ourselves.
There are only two people at a table for four.
There's plenty here, plenty there, plenty there, plenty there!
So that's how it is.
I can eat this, I can eat this, I can eat this, I can eat this!
I can't eat this.
What was your favorite work-related meal this year?What was your favorite work-related food this year?
Yes, I had Loki in Akita.
I was so surprised at how delicious the conger eel tempura I had there was!
Yes...
We ate it together.
We ate it together
We ate together.
Kabosuz.
Kabosuzu.
Kabosoz
Cabos Z
Arab
That was delicious.
I wonder what it was.
The ramen I had in New Zealand.
Yeah.
New Zealand's pretty good, isn't it?
It was great!
That's how I discovered venison... by myself.
I'd given it to Kii as a snack, but I'd never had it before.
I thought it was delicious, so I had to give some to Kii.
Kii? Give it to your dog, too.
Give it to Kii. I wonder if it's different from venison.
Yes, it is. It's a little fresher.
Kitty's a dog.Kii is a dog
Kii is a dog.
Are you wearing a black rice cake? Kitty, Kitty, Kitty.
Kitty's ass is always safe.
Kii wears glasses.
Kii, you're a beautiful human being.
Kii and Kui-chan, I hope you and your sister will be fans of the fast-eating contest.
I don't eat fast. If it's an oogie.
Let's all try it together.
Ayaka and Seitan's plan. We'll all eat pizza together.
There was a pizza a while back that weighed about a kilo and had three kinds of cheese on it.
And another A-size pizza. Who can eat the most?
What? Who can eat the most?
Ayaka's and Seita's
Ayaka's toseitan
Ayakacchan's toseitan
Ayakacchan's challenge
Ayaka's chicken bones
Can you guess who ate them?
Yashikoto-san and Nakayama-san ate eight pieces.
Eight pieces?
Because, you know, there's at least one.
That's right.
No, 8 slices.
Eight large slices? That's crazy!
It's like one slice.
And I didn't think I could eat that many.
It's finally delicious.
All right, everyone, let's put them in order now.
I'm gonna put them in order.At the Wanku Soba
Wanksoba at Wanksoba is good.
Next, Morioka.
It's in Yokohama, in DeVille... in Pana DeVille.
Wankusoba?
Wanksoba.
Dog?
Dog? Wanksoba in DeVille?
He said he thought maybe they'd open one near the Deville.
In Yokohama.
What? Deville's?
There was a lot of stuff there at the time.
Let's just stock up on this one and be done with it.
What? We're not going to do "Devil's Advocate.
We had a manager who used to be an AD for a TV show.
That's right.
Oh my God.
That's amazing.
When they wanted to shoot a V-shot, they had to make it realistic and big.
It was a real comic book and it was this big.
Thank you!
It's so professional!
Are you too thankful?
What's so great about it?
I don't know, it's just...
There's some kind of editing software that allows you to put it back in.
I can always go back to the video and say, "This part of this time, this part of this time, this part of this time...
I usually type it in verbatim or in text, but there's a picture of it.
And there were comments.
That's great!amazing (e.g. of strength)
That's great.
Because yesterday... in the college industry...
I mean, it's like, you know, it's just like, you know, it's like a little bit different position or something.
And the ones that were staged, they put text on them so you could tell what they were.
Wow.
This is amazing.
He was taking pictures of everything.
Like a picture.
It's like this one of some song.
I don't know how to do this.
Thank you.
That's great.
Okay, let's have Wang Hoss.
Okay, I'll get Wang Hoss to compare.
I'll tell you.
I'm sure you'll be able to tell me which one is...
I don't know.
I don't know...
I don't feel like eating yet.
When I'm with you...
When I'm with ice cream, I feel like I'm eating more sweets than before
Because if I eat, I have Gummi Man.
Because I have a great candy man here.
That's right.
I'll eat it all at Karasutatai's Mango
Quick!
Oh, you don't like it.Oh, you don't like it.
If you could have them set up the live delivery and do it all at your home.
Let's have them do it.
My nickname is Prince.
Oji.
He came from Oji Hoshino.
It came from them, Oji Hoshino-san.
Oji.
So, looking back on this past year, all we could finally talk about was food.
There is nothing.
The other day, my mom and Riko's mom got along well, and they went to Disney together.
Really?
What's that?
I thought Riko's mom was the most amazing.
I thought Riko's mom was great, too.
You haven't seen her.
You didn't?
No, no.
I'm talking about Ibichi's parents.
I'm not talking about her parents.
Parents.
What kind of skating was it?
Oh, yeah.
One year.
Did you hear?
Noriko was looking forward to it the most.Noriko was the one I was looking forward to the most.
Yeah.
What was she going to do? At first.
Before the spring tour in May/June, I asked her for roller shades to play with me after the spring tour.
I didn't receive it for about 3 months.
I didn't receive it for about three months.
We ordered from the same manufacturer, but only you didn't receive it.
That's right.
That's why,
I waited for three months once and it didn't arrive, so I gave up and asked again and again, and recently, it came.
It finally came. It arrived, so he went skating with me.
That's nice. Why did you go?
I went skating for three months.
I went right away.
Next time, let's go with Mr. Trance.
What are those? Roller skates, not roller plates?
Shoe roller skates. Shoes.
Oh, that. The ones on the back.
Not the ones on the sharings-ashlings, the ones that kids wear.
The kind that kids wear. They wear them on their shoulders,
You push the button, and they come right out. It comes out. It comes out.
The ones you can wear on your shoer skates. The one you can wear on your Schuyler skates.
Seek. Seek.
Falling? Before I fell.
I couldn't skate. Really?
You mean the kind that you have to wear protective gear?
No, I was like a kid who works at a supermarket.
I mean, the kind with sharings on the heels.
Oh, that's what I mean. Uh, that's what I mean.
They are temple people.
Kids slip like this sometimes.
Isn't that what you're saying?
That's it.
It's called a stiff hikaru game roller.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, I did that.
I guess not.
Heel roller.
Uh, no, no.
It's normally embedded inside.
Yes, it is.
Only in Italian shoes,
Heel roller.
Yes.
That's the one I did.
Oh, no, not that part.
It's going out of style.
We did the job.
We're proud of it, aren't we?
Akira and the others did it, too, from the beginning.
Yes, but Akira and the others, they all did spooning at all.
They seem to be having fun.
I went out of my way to find spoons and stuff to do,
I don't practice.
Why bother?
It takes 15 minutes.
Oh, really?
Twelve hours. Twelve hours, yes.
But that's all I did.
That's about all I did.
In 15 minutes.
And the day before, I had a job,
I had a rather carolish job,
It was pretty early in the morning,
Two, three hours before.
But we gathered quite early,
Akira and the others were also working.
Really, we started meeting at noon.
It was about 10 minutes.
It should have been a little later.
We had less than two hours.
What time did you get together?
I think it was around midnight.
No one likes to meet at 12:00.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
By all means, by all means, 1:00 p.m.
Everyone wanted 1:00 p.m.
I don't get it.
Why would anyone want to be on time?
We'll meet at 12:00 and gather at 1:00.
That was good.
I don't know, maybe we should start at 10:00,
Oh, man, oh, man.
I thought we were going to meet at 10:00,
I see. I see.
I was wondering why the meeting was so early.
Everyone's just getting together on a Thursday.
Oh, I see.
They came back after sunbathing the last part of the day.
That's right.
That's why we didn't stay that long.
Two hours.
I'm going to eat and go home.
I'm back.
The picnic, what, you bring your own food?
We brought our own food, or we bought food,
We stopped by and had a picnic.
They were eating carrots that Yuna made,
We did that.
Oh, yeah.
In Okinawa?
I don't want to know.
Know, know, know.
It's Azura.
It's very austere.
Ah, tonjyu.
Oh, tonjou.
Ah, tire wall and,
Daegu and,
Tonjyu.
Oh no.
Instagram,
How'd you eat that?
I feel like you're the chatty one.You are the chatty one.
When you take a picture, blur the rice balls.
Then blur it properly.
I wanted to say it's the coldest because it's cold.
I wanted to say it was the coldest because it was cold because it was cold.
Why did you blur the tonchibi?
The blue one is medicine.
It's amazing.
I was like, let's do it in a field day type of way.
The color system.
I'll bring a proper bat minton and do it.
It takes two hours, right?
Two hours.
You look sad.
Please do it in the spring.
Please do it newly.
Please do it new.
Let's do that.
I'll think about the soba noodles project, too.
You're going to do it, aren't you?
Yes, I will.
I hope all goes well in the 21st year.
There's still one month to go.
I don't have a one-man show or anything.
One-man show will be the last.
The last Okkilaz show?
Okkiraz is the last.
You're safe.
Is it a one-man show?Is he a one-man, that's what that is.
When you say "one-man," that's that?
October, right? When is the next show?
Yes, can I go now?
Not the next show.
Before that, we have a show in January.
Yes, for a year.
It's a year?
Second year.
Pia Arena.
At Pia Arena, MF.
New spring?
Show?
Flying high?
Dragon castle.
Okra?
Beyond that.
Yes, a foreign arts festival. Yes, there is.
A little bit is a little bit.
I thought it would be nice to do it at the beginning of the year, though we often did it at the end of the year.
I was thinking that it would take more time for everyone to get together at the beginning of the year.
That's true.
New Year's is a slow time, isn't it?
I'm free.
I don't know how to put it.
But you must be pretty busy since it's the beginning of the work week.
Well, yeah, but you know.
It's Saturday and Sunday.
You know what I mean. Because, you know, everybody's off until the 4th.Because, you know. Because, you know, everyone is off until about the 4th, right?
That's right.
Then you work a little harder, and then you go back to work,
And even if you work on the 5th, if you have Saturday and Sunday off, then you have Sunday and Monday off.
Oh!
Pearina says.
It's a coming-of-age ceremony.
And Pialina is very good sound and easy to see.
It's really nice.
I think it's easy to get to, so please come. Tickets are on sale now. Please come.
Thank you very much.
So you're on vacation, can everyone come?
Vacation, work, work, work.
Work, work, work.
We're just starting to prepare for the University Congress.
It started yesterday.
Yes. I think it's going to get more complicated from now on.
It's going to get more complicated.
I am hoping that at the end of the year, I will be able to talk about something that will break your expectations.
Please look forward to it.
By now, I'd like to congratulate you.
Oh, well.
That's right.
Appealing, right?
Well, I was thinking about the flat place, for example, last year, Kashiwagi's graduation and Yamada's entrance, and the time of Limmat the year before last, the first time three people entered,
In short, it's flat.
Well, I don't think we have had a flat university council since I wonder when we had a flat council.
That's right.That's right.
That's right.
No, really, so, no, I really can't remember, you know.
Yeah, I can't remember.
So it's like Y. Y.
It's been about six years. Yeah, about two.
Even that time in Makuhari, you know, because of that. Yes, yes.
What was before Makuhari? Before Makuhari was Makuhari.
Before that was probably the flattest?
Before that, when was the hottest one?
Oh, that's 2000...
20...
Oh, 19... 19... 19...
19. 19?
Oh, that 19? Jinchinji Temple is 19?
Yes. Yes.
18. 18.
I mean, you know, Ocean's Guide or something like that.
Oh, but it was 16 years or something like that, 16 years or something like that.
That's about it, so it's Saitama, isn't it?
If you think it's flat, maybe, yes, Ocean's Guide.
Ocean's Guide, sure. Probably up to about that.
Because if you don't go back, there is no such thing.
It's been a long time since I've been happy.
I'm in a really good state of mind,
I think I can show you something like that,
I hope you can look forward to it.
I hope you can look forward to it,
And, ah, let's do it,And, oh, c'mon,
Now! Now!
Now, this is the announcement.
This is the announcement? This is it?
You decided to do this? This is it?
This is all you have to say?
Yes. Okay, then.
Ready, go!
Close, close, close.
Read it out.
Ta-da-da-da-da.
Well, fan club only, can you see this?
I can't see it.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Here we go.
Yes, the fan club event is going to be held.
Yay!
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku, coming soon?
It's a self-study for Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku Ebisu members,
It's a holiday on the 23rd of February, 2024, a Friday.
It will be held at the Pacifico Yokohama National Great Hall.
Yes, that's good.
Great.
It's a self-study.
Yes.
Then, you're the chairman, right?
Yes, sir.Yes.
Let me explain about self-study.
In the past, self-study was called "self-study" for those who were produced by the members,
This time, the younger team and the older team will each come up with their own self-study, and the two groups will also come up with their own self-study,
So, we would like to make it a single performance, with an intermission, or a part and a half, or something like that,
I would like to make it like a member-produced performance.
Yes, I would like to make it like a member-produced performance.
And there will also be a send-off, right?
Yes.
After the performance, everyone will see the audience off, and we will have a chance for them to give their impressions of the show, something that is only possible at a fan club event.
The last self-study.
I can't remember anymore, but who was the last one?
I think we did it in 2019.
Where did you do it?
Kawasaki.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kawasaki, Kawasaki.
Kawasaki.
I don't remember anything.
Oh, I see.
More, more, more.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I really don't remember anything about Gusuku.
But you commented earlier that you are an uncle.
Yes, I decorated it for my husband.
I only have my bag, my bag.
Aya, I'm worried about you.
Aya is so normal, she doesn't remember the basics.
I can't talk about Aya, I can't talk about memories.
We all said, "Yeah, I'm worried about her, so I'm worried about her. We all said, eh, I'm curious, so I'm curious.
Oh, I'm curious.
Ew.
But you remember that you really care.
Yeah, it's strange.
I'm aware of it.
Yes, well, when I heard that it was voluntary, some people interpreted it as, "Well, we're separating them from their older sisters and younger sisters, so maybe they're not all going to be in it,
So, I asked them if they thought that since they were separated from their older sisters and younger sisters, they might not perform, or that not all of them would perform.
So, the setlist is planned by the younger sisters and performed by all 10 members, and the reverse is also true.
Yes, I think it will be fun.
I think it will be fun.
Because we are all doing it together. Because we're all thinking together.
I'm glad the morning is coming at such a good time.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Yes, it is.
Yes. And that thing. Tomorrow.
Tomorrow. Something is going to happen on the 10th or so.
If you had seen the evening, you would have known that, right? Yes, I did.
How much did you know? I think something will happen tomorrow at noon.
Yes, I think so. Don't miss it.
Maya's solo combo, right? Ayamanya Level 8 will be held on December 12,
This one will be on Nico Nico Live's Nicotro Channel,
This will be broadcast live on the same channel as the Okela Disco and other events,
Please look forward to it. Please look forward to it.
And the showroom is tomorrow, right? The showroom is tomorrow.
That's Okorikko. That's Okoriko.
I've never seen these two together. Yes, you have.I've never seen these two together. Yes, I have.
You've done it before, haven't you? Oh, really?
Yes.
Okorikko. You're a little cockroach.
Oh.
So, that was the overall loose distribution, but I'll see you later in the year,
I might still do it before the end of the year.
We will deliver the delivery again, but without a live performance. Please watch again.
So please check back tomorrow at 12:00.
So, that's all for us, ShoesEvitational.
Bye bye.